# CHRISTAN DE LUNA

### WEB DEVELOPER

Atlanta, GA cjdeluna95@gmail.com (770) 910-2701 linkedin.com/in/christan-de-luna github.com/cdeluna95 cdeluna95.github.io

# **SUMMARY**

A highly driven college graduate with two years of experience in information technology, specializing in software development. Upto-date with the web development industry, with demonstrated ability to create exquisite user interface and user experience design, while continuously improving back-end skills and adhering to best coding practices to meet the goal of becoming a full-stack developer. Excels as an individual contributor and in a collaborative team setting to ensure work efficiency and punctual delivery.

### **EDUCATION**

### Georgia Gwinnett College

December 2017

GPA: 3.76

B.S. Information Technology (Software Development)

Awards: Dean's List, President's List, Magna Cum Laude

Coursework: Advanced Programming, Advanced Databases, Web Development, Software Development, Software Testing & QA

# **EXPERIENCE**

### Turner Broadcasting System – Cartoon Network

January 2018 - May 2018

Web Developer Intern

- Performed a series of data migrations from a fully Java-based back-end to a Drupal CMA as part of Turner's initiative.
- Integrated Conviva's SDK on website's video player by interacting with its API and constructing a series of metadata objects.
- Implemented complex security protocol changes on CartoonNetwork.com ahead of the Chrome 68 update.
- Converted PSDs manually to front-end code by employing responsive web design on CartoonNetwork.com's Drupal site.
- Accomplished game launches, page updates, and various minor enhancements to aid in the development process.
- Worked in an Agile environment using Scrum and JIRA to collaborate with cross-functional teams.

### Turner Broadcasting System - Adult Swim

January 2017 - August 2017

#### Web Developer Intern

- Assisted in the development of weekly homepage updates and other webpages related to company shows and streams.
- Employed AJAX to interact with the Turner API and fetch data related to drawings submitted by visitors on the homepage.
- Implemented an interactive list of Adult Swim's projects with Vue.js in class-based syntax instead of just HTML and CSS.
- Performed QA tests on video player to ensure proper functionality, browser and device compatibility, and ad delivery.
- Accomplished data management in internal CMS, daily chat moderation, and online search of unwanted bootleg links.

### Innovagears

September 2016 – October 2016

### WordPress Developer Intern

- Developed, designed, and optimized client's website with WordPress and common web technologies.
- Used BugHerd to effectively communicate with the client, track assignments, and keep work flow going.

## **PROJECTS**

### Suri (Vue.js & Laravel)

- Used Axios and promises to send AJAX requests, consume REST API, and perform CRUD operations on student data.
- Configured routes with vue-router to update dashboard pages dynamically without reloads from the server.
- Designed the user interface and user experience in clean SASS with minimal Bootstrap.

### Xenoblade Chronicles Quiz (AngularJS)

 Built a quiz app on the front-end, and fetched hardcoded-JSON data to load questions and answers.

### Visual App (Ruby on Rails)

 Leveraged in-class knowledge and external resources to develop a visual image hosting app in a complete SDLC methodology.

## SKILLS

### Languages

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP, Ruby, SQL

### **Technologies**

Bootstrap, SASS, LESS, ES6+, jQuery, Vue, Laravel, Rails, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Oracle

#### Tools

Git, NPM, Bower, Gulp, Webpack, Heroku, AWS, S3, WordPress, Drupal, Photoshop, Google Analytics, GitHub, Bitbucket, JIRA

#### Concepts

Algorithms, Data Structures, OOP, SDLC, Agile, Scrum, UI/UX/Responsive/Graphic Design, SEO

#### Certifications

Microsoft Technology Associate: Networking Fundamentals, Oracle Database 11g: SQL Fundamentals I